# Fátima Jácobo Ruiz

FRONT END DEVELOPER & GRAPHIC DESIGNER



#### **ABOUT ME**

Graphic Designer and Front end Web Developer Junior. Graduate from Laboratoria Peru and Cibertec, expertise in design, layout and web development, with great managment of the main Graphic Design Software tools. My professional interests are related to UX/UI Design, Fashion marketing & communication and art direction. I am a proactive, self-taught and disciplined person who enjoys teamwork.



fatima.jacoboruiz@gmail.com



fatimajr.github.io/portfolio



966 100 983



Calle Fisher Mz.U Lte 16 Dpto 502 La Calera de la Merced Surquillo Lima, Perú.

# **Experience**

#### **GRAPHIC DESIGNER & CM**

GCT ASESORES Y CONSULTORES MARCH 2015 - JULY 2015

Pre professional Training Design of graphic pieces, diffusion and management of content in social

#### GRAPHIC DESIGNER

MUNICIPALIDAD DISTRITAL DE SALAVERRY OCTOBER 2015 - JANUARY 2016

Pre professional training Design of banners and flyers for campaigns and advertise.

# **Education**

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER JUNIOR | LABORATORIA JULY 2016 - DECEMBER 2016

Intensive web development Bootcamp for 6 months.

# DIPLOMAED IN GRAPHIC DESIGN INNOVATION | CIBERTEC

MARCH 2016 - JUNE 2016

Diplomaed as part of technical degree in Graphic Design.

Courses: Graphic Direction | Branding Design Managment | Final Project

### TECHNICAL DEGREE IN GRAPHIC DESIGN | CIBERTEC

MARCH 2013 - DECEMBER 2015

Technical specialization in Graphic Design during 6 semestral cycles.

### **Certifieds**

DESIGN ADOBE SUITE TRAINING

JUNE 2016 - DECEMBER 2016

BPRO+ | DESIGN TRAINING CENTER

ECCE | EXAMINATION FOR THE CERTIFICATE IN ENGLISH

MARCH 2016

EL CULTURAL CENTRO PERU ANO AMERICANO

#### Interests

Visual Design Art Direction
UX/UI Design Photography
Web Design Fashion Editorial
Web Development Fashion Window Dressing

### THANKS FOR YOUR TIME

Please contact me if you need more information about my background and qualifications.

FÁTIMA JÁCOBO R.

### **Skills**

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPMENT

RESPONSIVE DESIGN

GRAPHIC DESIGN

EDITORIAL DESIGN

WEB DESIGN

WEB LAYOUT

















